<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">Motion Eye</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Paramètres</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_device_detail">add_device_detail</string>
    <string name="device_label">Alias de l\'appareil</string>
    <string name="device_url">URL de l\'appareil avec http:// or https://</string>
    <string name="http_for_local_access">(Optionnel) Port (généralement 8765)</string>
    <string name="title_activity_web_motion_eye">web_motion_eye</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Bouton factice</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">CONTENU\nFACTICE</string>
    <string name="Camera_List">Liste de caméras</string>
    <string name="action_about">À propos</string>
    <string name="tut_sub_device_list">Appuyez une fois pour afficher en plein écran, maintenez enfoncé pour afficher les options de modification et de suppression\n\n
        Si cet appareil motionEye est protégé par mot de passe, entrez en plein écran, saisissez les informations d\'identification et cliquez sur
        \ "Remember Me \" pour enregistrer le mot de passe et connecter votre caméra motionEye sans entrer
        les informations d'identification à nouveau:)\n\n
        Cliquez sur le bouton moins pour masquer l'aperçu\n\n
        Pour plus d'informations, consultez la section Aide et FAQ en cliquant sur les boutons de menu dans le coin supérieur droit</string>
    <string name="tut_title_device_list">C\'est votre premier appareil</string>
    <string name="tut_title_add_button">Ajoutez votre premier appareil</string>
    <string name="tut_sub_add_button">Appuyez sur le bouton + pour commencer \nCe bouton peut être glissé/déposé</string>
    <string name="toast_added">Ajouté</string>
    <string name="warning_invalid_url">URL invalide !</string>
    <string name="warning_empty_url">URL vide !</string>
    <string name="warning_empty_label">Alias vide !</string>
    <string name="send_feedback">Envoyer votre réaction</string>
    <string name="https_github_com_sjwall">https://github.com/sjwall</string>
    <string name="credits">crédits</string>
    <string name="motion_eye_logo">MOTION_EYE_LOGO</string>
    <string name="app_created_by_jairaj_jangle">App crée par : Jairaj Jangle</string>
    <string name="cc_calin_crisan">Logo par Calin Crisan</string>
    <string name="email_icon">EMAIL_ICON</string>
    <string name="cancelled_toast">Annulé</string>
    <string name="connecting_mE">Connection à motionEye</string>
    <string name="connecting_gD">Connection à Google Drive</string>
    <string name="loading">Chargement…</string>
    <string name="steps_to_install_motioneye">Étapes pour installer motionEye</string>
    <string name="imageview_for_url_icon">C\'est l\'image de l\'icône de l\'URL</string>
    <string name="imageview_for_port_icon">C\'est l\'image de l\'icône du port HTTP</string>
    <string name="imageview_for_label_icon">C\'est l\'image de l\'icône de l\'alias</string>
    <string name="button_for_confirmation">Appuyez sur ce bouton pour confirmer l\'ajout de l\'appareil</string>
    <string name="button_for_cancellation">Appuyez sur ce bouton pour annuler</string>
    <string name="dummy_button_for_showcaseview">N\'appuyez pas sur ce bouton, il s\'agit juste d\'un bouton factive pour afficher le tutoriel</string>
    <string name="button_for_device_detail_intent">Pressez ce bouton pour ajouter une caméra réseau</string>
    <string name="inputlayout_for_label">Champ pour l\'alias</string>
    <string name="inputlayout_for_port">Champ pour le port</string>
    <string name="inputlayout_for_url">Champ pour l\'URL</string>
    <string name="constraintlayout_for_list_ad_and_etc">Il s\'agit que d\'une mise en page contenant d\'autres éléments de cet écran</string>
    <string name="for_displaying_ads_by_admob">Cliquez ici pour voir la pub</string>
    <string name="error_try_again">Erreur, essayez à nouveau</string>
    <string name="error_try_delete">Erreur lors de l\'édition, essayez de supprimer l\'appareil à nouveau</string>
    <string name="ok_do_not_show_again">OK, ne plus me montrer.</string>
    <string name="optional_drive_link_linked_to_motioneye">(Optionnel) Lien Drive lié à motionEye</string>
    <string name="tut_title_drive_icon">C\'est l\'icône de Google Drive</string>
    <string name="tut_sub_drive_icon">Cliquez pour accéder au dossier motionEye contenant les images et vidéos déclenchées par la détection de mouvement</string>
    <string name="invalid_drive_warning">Lien Google Drive invalide !</string>
    <string name="be_a_developer">Être développeur</string>
    <string name="button_for_cloud_drive">Bouton pour Google Drive</string>
    <string name="button_to_collapse_and_expand_stream_preview">Bouton permettant de masquer et d\'afficher l\'aperçu du flux</string>
    <string name="checkbox_to_select_specific_network_camera">Case à cocher pour sélectionner une caméra réseau spécifique</string>
    <string name="help_and_faq">Aide et FAQ</string>
    <string name="materialtaptargetprompt">MaterialTapTargetPrompt</string>
    <string name="apache_license">Licence Apache</string>
    <string name="icons">Icônes</string>
    <string name="app_version_text">Version de l\'App</string>
    <string name="button_to_go_back_to_home_screen">Bouton pour revenir à l\'écran d\'accueil</string>
    <string name="dash">-</string>
    <string name="drive_icon">Icône Drive</string>
    <string name="github_icon">GITHUB_ICON</string>
    <string name="are_you_enjoying">Appréciez-vous l\'application ?</string>
    <string name="cancel">Annuler</string>

    <!--Setting Screen related strings below-->
    <string name="summary_support">Une demande ? Nous sommes heureux de vous aider !</string>
    <string name="choose_email_client">Choisissez un client mail</string>
    <string name="summary_faq">Regardez la foire aux questions</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy" tools:ignore="StringFormatInvalid"><![CDATA[<!DOCTYPE html>
    <html>
    <head>
      <meta charset=\'utf-8\'>
      <meta name=\'viewport\' content=\'width=device-width\'>
    </head>
    <body>
    <h2>Privacy Policy</h2> <p>
                    FutureJJ built the motionEye app - HomeSurveillance System app as
                    an Open Source app. This SERVICE is provided by
                    FutureJJ at no cost and is intended for
                    use as is.
                  </p> <p>
                    This page is used to inform visitors regarding
                    my policies with the collection, use, and
                    disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use
                    my Service.
                  </p> <p>
                    If you choose to use my Service, then you agree
                    to the collection and use of information in relation to this
                    policy. The Personal Information that I collect is
                    used for providing and improving the Service.
                    I will not use or share your
                    information with anyone except as described in this Privacy
                    Policy.
                  </p> <p>
                    The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings
                    as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at
                    motionEye app - HomeSurveillance System unless otherwise defined in this Privacy
                    Policy.
                  </p> <p><strong>Information Collection and Use</strong></p> <p>
                    For a better experience, while using our Service,
                    I may require you to provide us with certain
                    personally identifiable information, including but not limited to nothing. The
                    information that I request will be
                    retained on your device and is not collected by me in any way.
                  </p> <p>
                    The app does use third party services that may collect
                    information used to identify you.
                  </p> <div><p>
                      Link to privacy policy of third party service providers
                      used by the app
                    </p> <ul><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----></ul></div> <p><strong>Log Data</strong></p> <p>
                    I want to inform you that whenever
                    you use my Service, in a case of an error in the
                    app I collect data and information (through third
                    party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data
                    may include information such as your device Internet
                    Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system
                    version, the configuration of the app when utilizing
                    my Service, the time and date of your use of the
                    Service, and other statistics.
                  </p> <p><strong>Cookies</strong></p> <p>
                    Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are
                    commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. These are
                    sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and
                    are stored on your device\'s internal memory.
                  </p> <p>
                    This Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly.
                    However, the app may use third party code and libraries that
                    use “cookies” to collect information and improve their
                    services. You have the option to either accept or refuse
                    these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your
                    device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be
                    able to use some portions of this Service.
                  </p> <p><strong>Service Providers</strong></p> <p>
                    I may employ third-party companies
                    and individuals due to the following reasons:
                  </p> <ul><li>To facilitate our Service;</li> <li>To provide the Service on our behalf;</li> <li>To perform Service-related services; or</li> <li>To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.</li></ul> <p>
                    I want to inform users of this
                    Service that these third parties have access to your
                    Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks
                    assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated
                    not to disclose or use the information for any other
                    purpose.
                  </p> <p><strong>Security</strong></p> <p>
                    I value your trust in providing us
                    your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use
                    commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember
                    that no method of transmission over the internet, or method
                    of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and
                    I cannot guarantee its absolute security.
                  </p> <p><strong>Links to Other Sites</strong></p> <p>
                    This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click
                    on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site.
                    Note that these external sites are not operated by
                    me. Therefore, I strongly advise you to
                    review the Privacy Policy of these websites.
                    I have no control over and assume no
                    responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or
                    practices of any third-party sites or services.
                  </p> <p><strong>Children’s Privacy</strong></p> <p>
                    These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13.
                    I do not knowingly collect personally
                    identifiable information from children under 13. In the case
                    I discover that a child under 13 has provided
                    me with personal information,
                    I immediately delete this from our servers. If you
                    are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child
                    has provided us with personal information, please contact
                    me so that I will be able to do
                    necessary actions.
                  </p> <p><strong>Changes to This Privacy Policy</strong></p> <p>
                    I may update our Privacy Policy from
                    time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page
                    periodically for any changes. I will
                    notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy
                    on this page. These changes are effective immediately after
                    they are posted on this page.
                  </p> <p><strong>Contact Us</strong></p> <p>
                    If you have any questions or suggestions about
                    my Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact
                    me at systems.sentinel@gmail.com.
    </body>
    </html>]]>
      </string>
    <string name="tnc"><![CDATA[<!DOCTYPE html>
    <html>
    <head>
      <meta charset=\'utf-8\'>
      <meta name=\'viewport\' content=\'width=device-width\'>
      </head>
    <body>
    <h2>Terms &amp; Conditions</h2> <p>
                    By downloading or using the app, these terms will
                    automatically apply to you – you should make sure therefore
                    that you read them carefully before using the app. You’re
                    not allowed to copy, or modify the app, any part of the app,
                    or our trademarks in any way. You’re not allowed to attempt
                    to extract the source code of the app, and you also
                    shouldn’t try to translate the app into other languages, or
                    make derivative versions. The app itself, and all the trade
                    marks, copyright, database rights and other intellectual
                    property rights related to it, still belong to
                    FutureJJ.
                  </p> <p>
                    FutureJJ is committed to ensuring that the app
                    is as useful and efficient as possible. For that reason, we
                    reserve the right to make changes to the app or to charge
                    for its services, at any time and for any reason. We will
                    never charge you for the app or its services without making
                    it very clear to you exactly what you’re paying for.
                  </p> <p>
                    The motionEye app - Home Surveillance System app stores and processes personal data
                    that you have provided to us, in order to provide
                    my Service. It’s your responsibility to keep your
                    phone and access to the app secure. We therefore recommend
                    that you do not jailbreak or root your phone, which is the
                    process of removing software restrictions and limitations
                    imposed by the official operating system of your device. It
                    could make your phone vulnerable to
                    malware/viruses/malicious programs, compromise your phone’s
                    security features and it could mean that the
                    motionEye app - Home Surveillance System app won’t work properly or at all.
                  </p> <p>
                    You should be aware that there are certain things that
                    FutureJJ will not take responsibility for.
                    Certain functions of the app will require the app to have an
                    active internet connection. The connection can be Wi-Fi, or
                    provided by your mobile network provider, but
                    FutureJJ cannot take responsibility for the
                    app not working at full functionality if you don’t have
                    access to Wi-Fi, and you don’t have any of your data
                    allowance left.
                  </p> <p></p> <p>
                    If you’re using the app outside of an area with Wi-Fi, you
                    should remember that your terms of the agreement with your
                    mobile network provider will still apply. As a result, you
                    may be charged by your mobile provider for the cost of data
                    for the duration of the connection while accessing the app,
                    or other third party charges. In using the app, you’re
                    accepting responsibility for any such charges, including
                    roaming data charges if you use the app outside of your home
                    territory (i.e. region or country) without turning off data
                    roaming. If you are not the bill payer for the device on
                    which you’re using the app, please be aware that we assume
                    that you have received permission from the bill payer for
                    using the app.
                  </p> <p>
                    Along the same lines, FutureJJ cannot always
                    take responsibility for the way you use the app i.e. You
                    need to make sure that your device stays charged – if it
                    runs out of battery and you can’t turn it on to avail the
                    Service, FutureJJ cannot accept
                    responsibility.
                  </p> <p>
                    With respect to FutureJJ’s responsibility for
                    your use of the app, when you’re using the app, it’s
                    important to bear in mind that although we endeavour to
                    ensure that it is updated and correct at all times, we do
                    rely on third parties to provide information to us so that
                    we can make it available to you.
                    FutureJJ accepts no liability for any loss,
                    direct or indirect, you experience as a result of relying
                    wholly on this functionality of the app.
                  </p> <p>
                    At some point, we may wish to update the app. The app is
                    currently available on Android – the requirements for
                    system (and for any additional systems we
                    decide to extend the availability of the app to) may change,
                    and you’ll need to download the updates if you want to keep
                    using the app. FutureJJ does not promise that
                    it will always update the app so that it is relevant to you
                    and/or works with the Android version that you have
                    installed on your device. However, you promise to always
                    accept updates to the application when offered to you, We
                    may also wish to stop providing the app, and may terminate
                    use of it at any time without giving notice of termination
                    to you. Unless we tell you otherwise, upon any termination,
                    (a) the rights and licenses granted to you in these terms
                    will end; (b) you must stop using the app, and (if needed)
                    delete it from your device.
                  </p> <p><strong>Changes to This Terms and Conditions</strong></p> <p>
                    I may update our Terms and Conditions
                    from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page
                    periodically for any changes. I will
                    notify you of any changes by posting the new Terms and
                    Conditions on this page. These changes are effective
                    immediately after they are posted on this page.
                  </p> <p><strong>Contact Us</strong></p> <p>
                    If you have any questions or suggestions about
                    my Terms and Conditions, do not hesitate to
                    contact me at systems.sentinel@gmail.com.
                  </p> <p>
    </body>
    </html>]]>
      </string>
    <!--Settings Screen related string above-->

    <!--Example Texts for custom_list_helpandfaq.xml-->
    <string name="Eg_HAF_Question">Q: Voici la question qui trouve sa répondu dans le TextView ci-dessous</string>
    <string name="Eg_HAF_Answer">R: Voici la réponse de la question ci-dessus.</string>
    <string name="Eg_custom_list_item_Label">Alias de l\'appareil ajouté</string>
    <string name="Eg_custom_list_item_URL">url_de_appareil_ajoute.com</string>
    <string name="key_send_feedback">key_send_feedback</string>
    <string name="key_fullscreen">key_fullscreen</string>
    <string name="title_privacy_policy">Politique de Confidentialité</string>
    <string name="title_tnc">Termes et Conditions</string>
    <string name="key_pp">key_pp</string>
    <string name="key_tnc">key_tnc</string>
    <string name="key_autoopen">key_autoopen</string>
    <string name="autoopen_summary">Ouvre automatiquement le flux des caméras lorsqu\'une seule caméras
        est présente</string>
    <string name="about_summary">L\'application motionEye permet d\'intéragir avec motion eye
        et les caméras réseau, le tout dans une seule application</string>
    <string name="fullscreen_summary">Cacher les boutons de navigation et faire en sorte que l\'application soit en plein écran lorsque la vidéo est en cours
        le flux est ouvert</string>
    <string name="pp_summary">Bon à savoir : Nous ne recueillons aucune donnée auprès de vous</string>
    <string name="key_rate_me">key_rate_me</string>
    <string name="rate_me_summary">Vous appréciez l\'app?</string>
    <string name="title_rate_me">Notez moi</string>
    <string name="uh_oh">Uh Oh!</string>
    <string name="connecting_uM">Mode inconnu</string>
    <string name="yes">Oui</string>
    <string name="no">Non</string>
    <string name="check_help_faq">Consultez l\'aide et la FAQ</string>
    <string name="page_error_dialog_message">Aidez-nous à résoudre ce problème en nous faisant part de vos commentaires</string>

    <!--Elements at even position are questions and at odd positions are answers-->
    <string-array name="QandAs">
        <!-- 1 -->
        <item>Q: L\'application ne se connecte pas à la caméra IP</item>
        <item>R: Vérifiez si vous avez correctement mentionné http:// ou https:// avant l\'url et le numéro de port
        par défaut, le numéro de port de motionEye est 8765, vous pouvez également saisir le numéro de port 8081 pour la diffusion en streaming uniquement</item>

        <item>Q: Je ne parviens pas à saisir le nom d\'utilisateur et le mot de passe de ma caméra motionEye</item>
        <item>A: Veuillez appuyer sur votre flux de caméra protégé par mot de passe pour l\'ouvrir en mode plein écran,
            remplissez le nom d\'utilisateur et le mot de passe et cochez l\'option Se souvenir de moi.
            Si cette option pour saisir le mot de passe n\'apparaît pas, cliquez sur l\'icône d\'administration en haut à gauche
            coin pour entrer le nom d\'utilisateur et le mot de passe</item>

        <!-- 2 -->
        <item>Q: L\'application crash fréquemment / je ne peux pas voir le flux de la caméra</item>
        <item>R: Vérifiez si l\'application Android System WebView de votre appareil est à jour, cliquez sur ce lien pour mettre l\'application à jour :
            https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.webview&amp;hl</item>

        <!-- 3 -->
        <item>Q: Les liens motionEye ne peuvent pas être ouverts en tant que liens globaux/port transféré.</item>
        <item>R: Pour accéder aux liens mondiaux, il faut d\'abord activer la redirection de port dans le routeur WiFi vers lequel le dispositif motionEye
            est connecté, pour un guide étape par étape, consultez ce lien :
            https://github.com/ccrisan/motioneyeos/issues/58</item>

        <!-- 4 -->
        <item>Q: Mon routeur WiFi ne prend pas en charge la redirection de port, mais je veux accéder à mon appareil photo dans le monde entier</item>
        <item>R: Consultez le site https://www.dataplicity.com/. Ils ont une méthode géniale pour fabriquer votre appareil MotionEye
        disponible dans le monde entier sans transfert de port réel</item>

        <!-- X -->
        <item>Q: Je suis confronté à un problème non mentionné</item>
        <item>R: N\'hésitez pas à nous contacter sur notre courrier électronique dans la section "À propos" avant de noter l\'application, nous corrigerons le problème dès que possible</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
