<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">Motion Eye</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Einstellungen</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_device_detail">add_device_detail</string>
    <string name="device_label">Gerätebezeichnung</string>
    <string name="device_url">Geräte-URL mit http:// oder https://</string>
    <string name="http_for_local_access">(Optional) Port (normalerweise 8765)</string>
    <string name="title_activity_web_motion_eye">web_motion_eye</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="Camera_List">Kameraliste</string>
    <string name="action_about">Über</string>
    <string name="tut_sub_device_list">Tippen Sie einmal, um den Vollbildmodus anzuzeigen. Halten Sie gedrückt, um die Bearbeitungs- und Löschoptionen anzuzeigen.\n\n
        Wenn dieses motionEye-Gerät kennwortgeschützt ist, geben Sie den Vollbildmodus ein, geben Sie die Anmeldeinformationen ein und klicken Sie auf
        "Remember Me", um das Passwort zu speichern und Ihre motionEye-Kamera ohne Eingabe anzuschließen
        die Anmeldeinformationen noch einmal :)\n\n
        Klicken Sie auf die Minus-Schaltfläche, um die Vorschau auszublenden\n\n
        Weitere Informationen finden Sie im Abschnitt Hilfe und FAQ, indem Sie auf die Menüschaltflächen in der oberen rechten Ecke klicken</string>
    <string name="tut_title_device_list">Dies ist dein erstes Gerät</string>
    <string name="tut_title_add_button">Füge dein erstes Gerät hinzu</string>
    <string name="tut_sub_add_button">Tippe auf den + Knopf um zu starten \nDieser Knopf unterstützt Drag and Drop.</string>
    <string name="toast_added">Hinzugefügt</string>
    <string name="warning_invalid_url">Ungültige URL!</string>
    <string name="warning_empty_url">Leere URL!</string>
    <string name="warning_empty_label">Leere Bezeichnung!</string>
    <string name="send_feedback">Feedback senden</string>
    <string name="https_github_com_sjwall">https://github.com/sjwall</string>
    <string name="credits">Danksagungen</string>
    <string name="motion_eye_logo">MOTION_EYE_LOGO</string>
    <string name="app_created_by_jairaj_jangle">App erstellt durch: Jairaj Jangle</string>
    <string name="cc_calin_crisan">Logo von Calin Crisan</string>
    <string name="email_icon">EMAIL_ICON</string>
    <string name="cancelled_toast">Abgebrochen</string>
    <string name="connecting_mE">motionEye verbinden </string>
    <string name="connecting_gD">Google Drive verbinden</string>
    <string name="loading">Lädt…</string>
    <string name="steps_to_install_motioneye">Schritte, um motionEye zu installieren</string>
    <string name="imageview_for_url_icon">This is image of url icon</string>
    <string name="imageview_for_port_icon">This is image of HTTP port icon</string>
    <string name="imageview_for_label_icon">This is image of label icon</string>
    <string name="button_for_confirmation">Diesen Knopf drücken um das Hinzufügen des Gerätes zu bestätigen</string>
    <string name="button_for_cancellation">Diesen Knopf drücken um abzubrechen</string>
    <string name="dummy_button_for_showcaseview">Diesen Knopf nicht drücken, das ist nur ein dummy-Knopf um das Tutorial anzuzeigen</string>
    <string name="button_for_device_detail_intent">Diesen Knopf drücken um eine Netzwerkkamera hinzuzufügen.</string>
    <string name="inputlayout_for_label">This is layout for label</string>
    <string name="inputlayout_for_port">This is layout for port</string>
    <string name="inputlayout_for_url">This is layout for url</string>
    <string name="constraintlayout_for_list_ad_and_etc">This is just a layout containing other elements of this screen</string>
    <string name="for_displaying_ads_by_admob">Press here to view the ad</string>
    <string name="error_try_again">Fehler, noch einmal versuchen</string>
    <string name="error_try_delete">Fehler beim Bearbeiten, versuche, das Gerät zu löschen und neu hinzuzufügen</string>
    <string name="ok_do_not_show_again">OK, nicht noch einmal zeigen.</string>
    <string name="optional_drive_link_linked_to_motioneye">(Optional) mit motionEye verknüpfter Drive-Link</string>
    <string name="tut_title_drive_icon">This is the Drive icon</string>
    <string name="tut_sub_drive_icon">Click to access motionEye drive folder to view videos and photos triggered by motion detection</string>
    <string name="invalid_drive_warning">Invalid Google drive link!</string>
    <string name="be_a_developer">Be a Developer</string>
    <string name="button_for_cloud_drive">Button for Cloud Drive</string>
    <string name="button_to_collapse_and_expand_stream_preview">Button to collapse and expand stream preview</string>
    <string name="checkbox_to_select_specific_network_camera">Checkbox to select specific network camera</string>
    <string name="help_and_faq">Hilfe und FAQ</string>
    <string name="materialtaptargetprompt">MaterialTapTargetPrompt</string>
    <string name="apache_license">Apache-Lizenz</string>
    <string name="icons">Icons</string>
    <string name="app_version_text">App-Version</string>
    <string name="button_to_go_back_to_home_screen">Button to go back to Home Screen</string>
    <string name="dash">-</string>
    <string name="drive_icon">Drive Icon</string>
    <string name="github_icon">GITHUB_ICON</string>
    <string name="are_you_enjoying">Gefällt dir die App?</string>
    <string name="cancel">Abbrechen</string>

    <!--Setting Screen related strings below-->
    <string name="summary_support">Irgendwelche Fragen? Wir sind froh, helfen zu können!</string>
    <string name="choose_email_client">E-Mail-Client auswählen</string>
    <string name="summary_faq">FAQ anschauen</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy" tools:ignore="StringFormatInvalid"><![CDATA[<!DOCTYPE html>
    <html>
    <head>
      <meta charset=\'utf-8\'>
      <meta name=\'viewport\' content=\'width=device-width\'>
    </head>
    <body>
    <h2>Privacy Policy</h2> <p>
                    FutureJJ built the motionEye app - HomeSurveillance System app as
                    an Open Source app. This SERVICE is provided by
                    FutureJJ at no cost and is intended for
                    use as is.
                  </p> <p>
                    This page is used to inform visitors regarding
                    my policies with the collection, use, and
                    disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use
                    my Service.
                  </p> <p>
                    If you choose to use my Service, then you agree
                    to the collection and use of information in relation to this
                    policy. The Personal Information that I collect is
                    used for providing and improving the Service.
                    I will not use or share your
                    information with anyone except as described in this Privacy
                    Policy.
                  </p> <p>
                    The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings
                    as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at
                    motionEye app - HomeSurveillance System unless otherwise defined in this Privacy
                    Policy.
                  </p> <p><strong>Information Collection and Use</strong></p> <p>
                    For a better experience, while using our Service,
                    I may require you to provide us with certain
                    personally identifiable information, including but not limited to nothing. The
                    information that I request will be
                    retained on your device and is not collected by me in any way.
                  </p> <p>
                    The app does use third party services that may collect
                    information used to identify you.
                  </p> <div><p>
                      Link to privacy policy of third party service providers
                      used by the app
                    </p> <ul><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----></ul></div> <p><strong>Log Data</strong></p> <p>
                    I want to inform you that whenever
                    you use my Service, in a case of an error in the
                    app I collect data and information (through third
                    party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data
                    may include information such as your device Internet
                    Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system
                    version, the configuration of the app when utilizing
                    my Service, the time and date of your use of the
                    Service, and other statistics.
                  </p> <p><strong>Cookies</strong></p> <p>
                    Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are
                    commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. These are
                    sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and
                    are stored on your device\'s internal memory.
                  </p> <p>
                    This Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly.
                    However, the app may use third party code and libraries that
                    use “cookies” to collect information and improve their
                    services. You have the option to either accept or refuse
                    these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your
                    device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be
                    able to use some portions of this Service.
                  </p> <p><strong>Service Providers</strong></p> <p>
                    I may employ third-party companies
                    and individuals due to the following reasons:
                  </p> <ul><li>To facilitate our Service;</li> <li>To provide the Service on our behalf;</li> <li>To perform Service-related services; or</li> <li>To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.</li></ul> <p>
                    I want to inform users of this
                    Service that these third parties have access to your
                    Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks
                    assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated
                    not to disclose or use the information for any other
                    purpose.
                  </p> <p><strong>Security</strong></p> <p>
                    I value your trust in providing us
                    your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use
                    commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember
                    that no method of transmission over the internet, or method
                    of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and
                    I cannot guarantee its absolute security.
                  </p> <p><strong>Links to Other Sites</strong></p> <p>
                    This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click
                    on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site.
                    Note that these external sites are not operated by
                    me. Therefore, I strongly advise you to
                    review the Privacy Policy of these websites.
                    I have no control over and assume no
                    responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or
                    practices of any third-party sites or services.
                  </p> <p><strong>Children’s Privacy</strong></p> <p>
                    These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13.
                    I do not knowingly collect personally
                    identifiable information from children under 13. In the case
                    I discover that a child under 13 has provided
                    me with personal information,
                    I immediately delete this from our servers. If you
                    are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child
                    has provided us with personal information, please contact
                    me so that I will be able to do
                    necessary actions.
                  </p> <p><strong>Changes to This Privacy Policy</strong></p> <p>
                    I may update our Privacy Policy from
                    time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page
                    periodically for any changes. I will
                    notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy
                    on this page. These changes are effective immediately after
                    they are posted on this page.
                  </p> <p><strong>Contact Us</strong></p> <p>
                    If you have any questions or suggestions about
                    my Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact
                    me at systems.sentinel@gmail.com.
    </body>
    </html>]]>
      </string>
    <string name="tnc"><![CDATA[<!DOCTYPE html>
    <html>
    <head>
      <meta charset=\'utf-8\'>
      <meta name=\'viewport\' content=\'width=device-width\'>
      </head>
    <body>
    <h2>Terms &amp; Conditions</h2> <p>
                    By downloading or using the app, these terms will
                    automatically apply to you – you should make sure therefore
                    that you read them carefully before using the app. You’re
                    not allowed to copy, or modify the app, any part of the app,
                    or our trademarks in any way. You’re not allowed to attempt
                    to extract the source code of the app, and you also
                    shouldn’t try to translate the app into other languages, or
                    make derivative versions. The app itself, and all the trade
                    marks, copyright, database rights and other intellectual
                    property rights related to it, still belong to
                    FutureJJ.
                  </p> <p>
                    FutureJJ is committed to ensuring that the app
                    is as useful and efficient as possible. For that reason, we
                    reserve the right to make changes to the app or to charge
                    for its services, at any time and for any reason. We will
                    never charge you for the app or its services without making
                    it very clear to you exactly what you’re paying for.
                  </p> <p>
                    The motionEye app - Home Surveillance System app stores and processes personal data
                    that you have provided to us, in order to provide
                    my Service. It’s your responsibility to keep your
                    phone and access to the app secure. We therefore recommend
                    that you do not jailbreak or root your phone, which is the
                    process of removing software restrictions and limitations
                    imposed by the official operating system of your device. It
                    could make your phone vulnerable to
                    malware/viruses/malicious programs, compromise your phone’s
                    security features and it could mean that the
                    motionEye app - Home Surveillance System app won’t work properly or at all.
                  </p> <p>
                    You should be aware that there are certain things that
                    FutureJJ will not take responsibility for.
                    Certain functions of the app will require the app to have an
                    active internet connection. The connection can be Wi-Fi, or
                    provided by your mobile network provider, but
                    FutureJJ cannot take responsibility for the
                    app not working at full functionality if you don’t have
                    access to Wi-Fi, and you don’t have any of your data
                    allowance left.
                  </p> <p></p> <p>
                    If you’re using the app outside of an area with Wi-Fi, you
                    should remember that your terms of the agreement with your
                    mobile network provider will still apply. As a result, you
                    may be charged by your mobile provider for the cost of data
                    for the duration of the connection while accessing the app,
                    or other third party charges. In using the app, you’re
                    accepting responsibility for any such charges, including
                    roaming data charges if you use the app outside of your home
                    territory (i.e. region or country) without turning off data
                    roaming. If you are not the bill payer for the device on
                    which you’re using the app, please be aware that we assume
                    that you have received permission from the bill payer for
                    using the app.
                  </p> <p>
                    Along the same lines, FutureJJ cannot always
                    take responsibility for the way you use the app i.e. You
                    need to make sure that your device stays charged – if it
                    runs out of battery and you can’t turn it on to avail the
                    Service, FutureJJ cannot accept
                    responsibility.
                  </p> <p>
                    With respect to FutureJJ’s responsibility for
                    your use of the app, when you’re using the app, it’s
                    important to bear in mind that although we endeavour to
                    ensure that it is updated and correct at all times, we do
                    rely on third parties to provide information to us so that
                    we can make it available to you.
                    FutureJJ accepts no liability for any loss,
                    direct or indirect, you experience as a result of relying
                    wholly on this functionality of the app.
                  </p> <p>
                    At some point, we may wish to update the app. The app is
                    currently available on Android – the requirements for
                    system (and for any additional systems we
                    decide to extend the availability of the app to) may change,
                    and you’ll need to download the updates if you want to keep
                    using the app. FutureJJ does not promise that
                    it will always update the app so that it is relevant to you
                    and/or works with the Android version that you have
                    installed on your device. However, you promise to always
                    accept updates to the application when offered to you, We
                    may also wish to stop providing the app, and may terminate
                    use of it at any time without giving notice of termination
                    to you. Unless we tell you otherwise, upon any termination,
                    (a) the rights and licenses granted to you in these terms
                    will end; (b) you must stop using the app, and (if needed)
                    delete it from your device.
                  </p> <p><strong>Changes to This Terms and Conditions</strong></p> <p>
                    I may update our Terms and Conditions
                    from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page
                    periodically for any changes. I will
                    notify you of any changes by posting the new Terms and
                    Conditions on this page. These changes are effective
                    immediately after they are posted on this page.
                  </p> <p><strong>Contact Us</strong></p> <p>
                    If you have any questions or suggestions about
                    my Terms and Conditions, do not hesitate to
                    contact me at systems.sentinel@gmail.com.
                  </p> <p>
    </body>
    </html>]]>
      </string>
    <!--Settings Screen related string above-->

    <!--Example Texts for custom_list_helpandfaq.xml-->
    <string name="Eg_HAF_Question">Q: Here goes the question which is answered in the TextView Below</string>
    <string name="Eg_HAF_Answer">A: Here goes the answer to the question above.</string>
    <string name="Eg_custom_list_item_Label">Label of added device</string>
    <string name="Eg_custom_list_item_URL">url_of_added_device.com</string>
    <string name="key_send_feedback">key_send_feedback</string>
    <string name="key_fullscreen">key_fullscreen</string>
    <string name="title_privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="title_tnc">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="key_pp">key_pp</string>
    <string name="key_tnc">key_tnc</string>
    <string name="key_autoopen">key_autoopen</string>
    <string name="autoopen_summary">Automatically opens camera stream when only one camera device
        is present</string>
    <string name="about_summary">The motionEye app is an interface to interact with the motion eye
        powered and other network cameras, all in one app</string>
    <string name="fullscreen_summary">Hide navigation buttons and make app fullscreen when video
        stream is opened</string>
    <string name="pp_summary">Good to Know: We do not collect any data from you</string>
    <string name="key_rate_me">key_rate_me</string>
    <string name="rate_me_summary">Enjoying the app?</string>
    <string name="title_rate_me">Rate me</string>
    <string name="uh_oh">Oh oh!</string>
    <string name="connecting_uM">Unknown Mode</string>
    <string name="yes">Ja</string>
    <string name="no">Nein</string>
    <string name="check_help_faq">Überprüfe die Hilfe und die FAQ</string>
    <string name="page_error_dialog_message">Please help us fix the issue by letting us know by sending a feedback</string>

    <!--Elements at even position are questions and at odd positions are answers-->
    <string-array name="QandAs">
        <item>Q: App verbindet sich nicht mit der Netzwerkkamera</item>
        <item>A: Überprüfe, dass sich http:// oder https:// vor der URL befindet und der Port verwendet wird.
        (motionEye Standardeinstellung: 8765 oder 8081 um nur zu streamen)</item>

        <item>Q: Ich kann keinen Benutzernamen und kein Passwort für meine motionEye-Kamera eingeben</item>
        <item>A: Tippen Sie auf Ihren passwortgeschützten Kamerastream, um ihn im Vollbildmodus zu öffnen.
            Geben Sie den Benutzernamen und das Passwort ein und aktivieren Sie die Option "Angemeldet bleiben".
            Wenn diese Option zur Eingabe des Kennworts nicht angezeigt wird, klicken Sie oben links auf das Administrationssymbol
            Ecke, um den Benutzernamen und das Passwort einzugeben</item>

        <item>Q: App hängt sich oft auf / Ich kann den Kamerastream nicht anschauen</item>
        <item>A: Check whether the Android System WebView app in your device is up to date, check this link to update the app:
            https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.webview&amp;hl</item>

        <item>Q: motionEye links cannot be opened as global links/port forwarded</item>
        <item>A: To access global links, first enable port forwarding in the WiFi router to which motionEye device
            is connected, for step by step guide checkout this link:
            https://github.com/ccrisan/motioneyeos/issues/58</item>

        <item>Q: My WiFi router does not support Port forwarding but I want to access my camera globally</item>
        <item>A: Check out https://www.dataplicity.com/ they have an awesome method to make your motionEye device
        available globally without actual port forwarding</item>

        <item>Q: I am facing an unmentioned problem</item>
        <item>A: Please consider contacting us on our feedback mail in the About section before rating the app, we will fix the issue as soon as possible</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
